anyquestion.wiki 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy

### Welcome to AnyQuestion!

AnyQuestion.wiki, Inc. ("AnyQuestion.wiki") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about AnyQuestion.wiki's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how AnyQuestion.wiki receives, collects and uses information in connection with your visit to its website accessed at www.AnyQuestion.wiki ("Website") and through Your use of the AnyQuestion.wiki.

#### 1\. Website Visitors: Collection and Use of Your Information

**Information You Provide:**

Except as explicitly described below, you can use the Website and access the Browser (collectively, "Service") without providing any personally identifying information such as names, email addresses, and phone numbers ("Personal Information").

**Information We Automatically Collect:**

AnyQuestion.wiki does not automatically collect any Personal Information on or through the Website, except as may be provided by you in connection with your voluntary communications with AnyQuestion.wiki. However, when you visit the Website, AnyQuestion.wiki may automatically collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use of the Website. For example, AnyQuestion.wiki may use "cookies", "web beacons" and similar devices to track your activities as a visitor to the Website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record- keeping purposes. A web-beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at the Website. Cookies may be used to analyze Website usage, improve content, customize the Website's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. AnyQuestion.wiki's use of cookies or similar devices is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

When you visit the Website, AnyQuestion.wiki may also automatically receive and record certain other non- personally identifiable information of the type that servers typically collect on AnyQuestion.wiki server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpages that you visit. AnyQuestion.wiki collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the Website, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. AnyQuestion.wiki will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with the aggregate data of its users. Please be aware that some non-personally identifiable information such as Uniform Resource Locators ("URL's") or Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses could become Personal Information when combined by third parties with the ISP's records. AnyQuestion.wiki does NOT do this with your information.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

AnyQuestion.wiki does not rent, sell, or share any information about you with any third-parties. Torch may disclose your information if AnyQuestion.wiki believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on AnyQuestion.wiki; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AnyQuestion.wiki (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AnyQuestion.wiki services or members of the public.

AnyQuestion.wiki may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help it provide, analyze and improve the Website and Browser (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, information processing and improvement of the Website's features and services. These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on behalf of AnyQuestion.wiki and under obligations similar to those in this Policy.

We may allow third parties, including advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our website and Applications. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements.

**Third party advertisers and websites**

If you access another website through the Website and that website is operated by any entity other than AnyQuestion.wiki, that site is referred to as a "Third Party Site". Unless AnyQuestion.wiki clearly indicates otherwise at the time of collection, AnyQuestion.wiki does not share Personal Information with Third Party Sites. Please be aware however that these Third Party Sites may collect information about you. Please see the Third Party Site's privacy policy to better understand what information is collected, how it is used and shared, and your choices regarding control. AnyQuestion.wiki has no control over these linked Third Party Sites, each of which has a separate privacy and data collection practice, independent of this Policy. AnyQuestion.wiki does not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any Third Party Site. As such, AnyQuestion.wiki is not responsible for, nor have control over, the content or the privacy policies of these Third Party Sites. You must read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit when linking from the Website. This Policy applies solely to information collected by AnyQuestion.wiki.

#### 2\. AnyQuestion.wiki: Collection and Use of Your Information

**Information AnyQuestion.wiki receives when you use the website**

You do not need to provide any Personal Information in order to download or use the Browser.  
When you use the Browser (like most other web browsers), AnyQuestion.wiki may automatically receive non- personally identifiable information, such as your system's IP address, when you contact our servers and any cookies attached to such search from third parties. AnyQuestion.wiki itself does not set any cookies.

However, if you use the "Share" feature that links the Website URL to your personal Facebook or Twitter page, you will be asked to provide certain Personal Information, which will include your username and password, in order to link with your Facebook or Twitter account. This information is transmitted directly to the respective social network. AnyQuestion.wiki does not store this information. It is entirely optional for you to use the 'Share' feature or any other Browser features that AnyQuestion.wiki may make available to you.

**Information AnyQuestion.wiki sends to websites and ISPs**

Like most web browsers, the websites that you visit using the AnyQuestion.wiki will receive certain non- personally identifiable information, for example, this information may consist of the type of browser, type of device, language preference, the referring website and your IP address. These sites may also set their own cookies or other website data on your system. Each website determines its own privacy practices and is not controlled or monitored by AnyQuestion.wiki. If you want to understand how these websites use your information, you must review that particular website's privacy policy.

**Information AnyQuestion.wiki Stores when you use the Browser**

Unless you are in Incognito Mode (see below), the AnyQuestion.wiki stores some of your information locally on your system. For example, the AnyQuestion.wiki may store basic browsing history such as URL's of pages you visit, text and images from those pages, IP addresses linked from the pages, index of most pages you visit, cookies deposited on your system by and a record of downloads you have made.

You have the ability to conduct searches through an "Incognito Mode". When you use the Incognito Mode the websites you visit and files you download are not recorded in your browsing and download history by the AnyQuestion.wiki. Websites you visit may deposit new cookies on your system while you are in Incognito Mode, but these cookies will be deleted after you close all your incognito windows. Of course the websites you have visited may still have a record of your visit to their website. Also, when you exit the Incognito Mode, any files saved to your computer will remain on your computer.

**AnyQuestion.wiki's Torrent Feature**

The AnyQuestion.wiki features a "Torrent" software plug-in. This feature downloads files quickly by trading pieces with other users who are also downloading (or have downloaded) the same content. Your use of AnyQuestion.wiki's Torrent feature to download your queries and result files will, in turn, enable other AnyQuestion.wiki users (or users of other clients that communicate using the torrent protocol, including clients that are unaffiliated with AnyQuestion.wiki) to download pieces of those files from you. Although your IP address is associated with your piece of the file, other users will not have access to any other Personal Information about you.

We do not track the files that you transfer with AnyQuestion.wiki's Torrent feature. Your use of AnyQuestion.wiki's Torrent feature does not create a record of which files you transfer to be kept by AnyQuestion.wiki or on behalf of any third party.

#### 3\. Additional Privacy Information for the Website and Browser

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. AnyQuestion.wiki operates its Website and Browser in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The Website and Browser are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that such individuals do not provide any personally indentifying information through the Website.

**Security**

AnyQuestion.wiki takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although AnyQuestion.wiki cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, AnyQuestion.wiki has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE WEBSITE FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICES, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS POLICY, AND ANYQUESTION.WIKI'S TERMS OF USE, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER. ADDITIONALLY, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO AND PROCESSED IN COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR COUNTRY.

**Data Retention**

AnyQuestion.wiki will retain your information for only as long as needed to provide you services and fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy. AnyQuestion.wiki may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with its legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce its agreements. Consistent with these requirements, AnyQuestion.wiki will try to delete your information as quickly as possible.

**Business Transitions**

In the event that AnyQuestion.wiki goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. AnyQuestion.wiki will post a notice on this Website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information AnyQuestion.wiki may have prior to such transfer.

**Changes to Policy**

From time to time, AnyQuestion.wiki may revise this Policy. AnyQuestion.wiki will post the revised Policy on the Website, so that users can always be aware of what information AnyQuestion.wiki collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. AnyQuestion.wiki will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, AnyQuestion.wiki will provide more prominent notice. You should also visit this page periodically to review any changes to this Policy.

**Contact Information**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact AnyQuestion.wiki at privacy@AnyQuestion.wiki.
